<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>design on Arvin Das</title>
    <link>https://thearvindas.github.io/tags/design/</link>
    <description>Recent content in design on Arvin Das</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© {year}</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Jul 2021 09:19:29 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://thearvindas.github.io/tags/design/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>I&#39;m Now on Dribbble!</title>
      <link>https://thearvindas.github.io/blog/im-now-on-dribbble/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jul 2021 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thearvindas.github.io/blog/im-now-on-dribbble/</guid>
      <description>It’s been a couple of days since I’ve started out on Dribbble, and I must say, it’s been an exciting experience. It’s incredible to see so much creativity, ideas, mockups, everything-cool-about-design all in one place.
Seeing everyone’s work, I decided I needed something to show for as well; hence, I began making mini-projects. I’ve made two so far, really proud of how they’ve come out!
Neon Blue Login/Sign-Up Zomato — Dark Theme RevampCheck them out on my Dribbble here !</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I&#39;ve Started Learning Figma</title>
      <link>https://thearvindas.github.io/blog/ive-started-learning-figma/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jun 2021 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thearvindas.github.io/blog/ive-started-learning-figma/</guid>
      <description>The more I&amp;rsquo;ve been exploring the world of design, the more I&amp;rsquo;ve realized the immense power of Figma. Naturally, I had to get my hands dirty right away.
I play around with Adobe Ps and Ai quite often, so it didn&amp;rsquo;t take too much time to get going with Figma. I was immediately amazed by the brilliant workflow, tools, and simply the experience of using it. I watched a few YouTube videos to understand how things work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Took a Foundations of UX Design Course — Here&#39;s What I Learnt</title>
      <link>https://thearvindas.github.io/blog/foundations-of-ux-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2021 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thearvindas.github.io/blog/foundations-of-ux-design/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve always been a huge fan of design. The moment I got some free time, I made sure to make the most out of it — I took this course on Coursera and wrote down what I found most important so as to document my learnings as well as, maybe, pass it on =)
Here&amp;rsquo;s what I learnt. 
 What is UX? 
UX stands for User Experience. It is how a user feels about interacting with or experiencing a product.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
