<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on Arvin Das</title>
    <link>https://thearvindas.github.io/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on Arvin Das</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© {year}</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 00:19:29 +0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://thearvindas.github.io/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>a recap, my first internship, and the pursuit of happyness</title>
      <link>https://thearvindas.github.io/blog/a-recap-my-first-internship-and-the-pursuit-of-happyness/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 00:19:29 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thearvindas.github.io/blog/a-recap-my-first-internship-and-the-pursuit-of-happyness/</guid>
      <description>Since a lot of what I&amp;rsquo;ve wrote down in this blog is my attempt at getting an internship, it makes sense to have a post celebrating that I&amp;rsquo;ve finally got one :D
Stoked to announce that I&amp;rsquo;ve joined Zuperly as a Product intern! It&amp;rsquo;s been nearly 2 weeks since I&amp;rsquo;ve joined and I&amp;rsquo;ve had a fantastic experience so far. Huge huge thanks to the founder Kapil who&amp;rsquo;s made it so so easy for me to jump in on this and get started.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>my favourite reads, tools, and other random things on the internet [keeps updating]</title>
      <link>https://thearvindas.github.io/blog/internet-gratitude-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 05:19:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thearvindas.github.io/blog/internet-gratitude-list/</guid>
      <description>The following is a non-exhaustive gratitude list [keeps updating] of all my favourite reads, websites, tools, and any other random thing I&amp;rsquo;ve found on the internet that has helped me make my life better.
reads  The Theory of Cumulative Stress: How to Recover When Stress Builds — James Clear → great read about how stress builds up and how you can fight back Landing at Razorpay — Manan Agarwal → fantastic read about hard work, humility, and trusting the process Rules — Aditya Mohanty → this read is what inspired me to define rules for my own life From Fool To Cool: How To Stay Calm, No Matter What — Bruce Kasanoff → fascinating read about staying calm Lines, not dots — Manas Saloi → a great post (as always from Manas) about building professional relationships Tonkin&amp;rsquo;s Model of Grief — Lois Tonkin → a read about Tonkin&amp;rsquo;s Model of Grief 100 Simple Truths — traf → the cut-throat truth laid down  tools  Markdown New Tab → love using this for my new tabs, easy to jot down to-dos, reminders, etc Visualize Value → when I&amp;rsquo;m not using Markdown New Tab, Visualize Value is my go to extension for new tabs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>rules, why I need them, and why I&#39;m writing them down [keeps updating]</title>
      <link>https://thearvindas.github.io/blog/rules/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2021 05:19:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thearvindas.github.io/blog/rules/</guid>
      <description>A while ago, I stumbled across Aditya Mohanty&amp;rsquo;s blog and saw this — a collection of rules that he lives by. Being someone that loves defining every aspect of my life and committing to a certain standard of ethics, I decided to make a list of rules for myself as well.
To save your time, I&amp;rsquo;ve listed my rules first, the chit-chat comes later.
Rules [last updated on Dec 16, 2021]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>upraised, embark, and a small step ahead</title>
      <link>https://thearvindas.github.io/blog/upraised-embark-and-a-small-step-ahead/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2021 05:19:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thearvindas.github.io/blog/upraised-embark-and-a-small-step-ahead/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve always been an ardent fan of trusting the process. It&amp;rsquo;s easy to get disheartened when things don&amp;rsquo;t seem to work out but it&amp;rsquo;s important to believe that everyone has a story, a process, a journey towards what they want to achieve — trust it and never stop the hard work.
Yesterday came the good news of me clearing Upraised&amp;rsquo;s internship program called Embark . I was selected as one of the top 50 in the Design track among a total of 4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5w1h, user stories, and defining KPIs</title>
      <link>https://thearvindas.github.io/blog/5w1h-user-stories-and-defining-kpis/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2021 00:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thearvindas.github.io/blog/5w1h-user-stories-and-defining-kpis/</guid>
      <description>These are my notes from Solving Product Design Exercises by Artiom Dashinsky .
approaching a product design exercise Whenever you encounter a problem, don&amp;rsquo;t immediately dive into it and start thinking of solutions. The single most important thing to remember while solving product design exercises is to follow a process. Here are three tips to help you solve a problem:
  Make sure you understand the task: understand the deliverables, mode of delivery, fidelity level required, and the mode of presentation</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>jackets, letters, and miles to go before I sleep</title>
      <link>https://thearvindas.github.io/blog/jackets-letters-and-miles-to-go-before-i-sleep/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2021 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thearvindas.github.io/blog/jackets-letters-and-miles-to-go-before-i-sleep/</guid>
      <description>I leave home for college tomorrow. Lots of emotions running around in my head. Thought I&amp;rsquo;d document a bit of it.
The pandemic changed the way college works. I&amp;rsquo;ve spent more time at home than in Manipal so far in my Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s. The norm has shifted. Home is where I live, Manipal is the vacation. It&amp;rsquo;s difficult for my family to see me packing my bags and looking up flights online.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>productivity, leaning forward, and pomodoro</title>
      <link>https://thearvindas.github.io/blog/productivity-leaning-forward-and-pomodoro/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thearvindas.github.io/blog/productivity-leaning-forward-and-pomodoro/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been going down for walks these days and have picked up a habit of listening to podcasts. Today I listened to this podcast by Rob Dial where he speaks about 6 habits to boost one&amp;rsquo;s productivity. Here&amp;rsquo;s what I learnt:
Everyone has 24 hours in a day. The difference is in how these 24 hours are spent. To be productive is to maximize outcomes in the time we have — getting more things done in the same amount of time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>high agency, the PM craft, and great people</title>
      <link>https://thearvindas.github.io/blog/high-agency-the-pm-craft-and-great-people/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2021 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thearvindas.github.io/blog/high-agency-the-pm-craft-and-great-people/</guid>
      <description>Recently watched this video of Shreyas Doshi talking about his PM learnings over the years, and immediately knew I had to document it right away.
Here are my notes from the video:
Advice for aspiring PMs:
 Do the role before you get the job Your current company/work is the best place to start Build your own side project/product  The Law of PM Suitability: the traits required to break into the PM role are the very same traits that are prerequisites for succeeding as a PM</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>hunting, shipwrecks, and a washed out Grand Prix</title>
      <link>https://thearvindas.github.io/blog/hunting-shipwrecks-and-a-washed-out-grand-prix/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thearvindas.github.io/blog/hunting-shipwrecks-and-a-washed-out-grand-prix/</guid>
      <description>Before I begin, here are a few things I&amp;rsquo;d like to clear up:
 I&amp;rsquo;ve been noticing that the titles of these blog posts have been increasing in length each time. Although I would like them all to be the same length simply for good visuals, I can&amp;rsquo;t find a way to keep them concise. Hence, if you&amp;rsquo;re looking at the list of posts and noticing the gradual increase, don&amp;rsquo;t worry, it&amp;rsquo;s been bothering me too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>cold emails, metrics, and root cause analysis</title>
      <link>https://thearvindas.github.io/blog/cold-emails-metrics-and-root-cause-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2021 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thearvindas.github.io/blog/cold-emails-metrics-and-root-cause-analysis/</guid>
      <description>At the start of 2021, I promised myself I&amp;rsquo;d do a few things for sure this year. Excited to tell y&amp;rsquo;all that I&amp;rsquo;ve ticked off a checkbox—sending a cold email. I was hesitant to apply for internships over the last few months due to a fear of a lack of knowledge. I can now tell you in all honesty that, that is time gone down the drain. No regrets because I&amp;rsquo;ve learnt a lot, nevertheless.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>inconvenient truths, discovery, and the 21 laws</title>
      <link>https://thearvindas.github.io/blog/inconvenient-truths-discovery-and-the-21-laws/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Aug 2021 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thearvindas.github.io/blog/inconvenient-truths-discovery-and-the-21-laws/</guid>
      <description>inconvenient truth about productsproduct discovery--The more I dive into learning and understanding product, the more I understand how important reading is. I&amp;rsquo;ve come across some incredible reads in the past week, some of which I&amp;rsquo;d like to put out here.
I&amp;rsquo;ve said incredible reads, I&amp;rsquo;m sure some of y&amp;rsquo;all must be thinking, &amp;ldquo;oh, Arvin read something by Marty Cagan &amp;rdquo;. Damn right you are.
This article titled The Inconvenient Truth About Product speaks about the unavoidable, annoying, yet very real truth about building product.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>olympics, slack, and atomic habits</title>
      <link>https://thearvindas.github.io/blog/olympics-slack-and-atomic-habits/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Aug 2021 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thearvindas.github.io/blog/olympics-slack-and-atomic-habits/</guid>
      <description>The Olympics have come to an end and what an incredible few weeks it has been. I&amp;rsquo;ve always loved sports. I started playing football for my neighbourhood team—Yellowbird Soccer—when I was 7. I&amp;rsquo;ll be honest, we didn&amp;rsquo;t win too much, but some of my fondest memories growing up are with this team. My dad was one of the coaches, and I vividly remember how we used to go to the ground early, lugging a bag with around 15 footballs, carrying marking cones and snacks for the team in a portable freezer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>kick-off, git, and summer break&#39;21</title>
      <link>https://thearvindas.github.io/blog/kick-off-git-and-summer-break-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Aug 2021 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thearvindas.github.io/blog/kick-off-git-and-summer-break-21/</guid>
      <description>Hello!insert drumroll, perhaps some applause
(Just kidding.)
I am so, so pumped to be writing the first blog for my website. Building something of my own has always been this huge goal of mine and to see thearvindas.me come to life is unreal to me.
The process started way back at the start of June. I started looking up static site generators and, needless to say, I was very flustered by the endless resources and results.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
