<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>notes on Arvin Das</title>
    <link>https://thearvindas.github.io/tags/notes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in notes on Arvin Das</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© {year}</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 00:19:29 +0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://thearvindas.github.io/tags/notes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>hooked, the ikea effect, and the manipulation matrix</title>
      <link>https://thearvindas.github.io/blog/hooked-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 00:19:29 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thearvindas.github.io/blog/hooked-notes/</guid>
      <description>Here are my notes/highlights/favourite parts from Hooked by Nir Eyal:
  Face it, we’re hooked. The technologies we use have turned into compulsions, if not full-fledged addictions. It’s the impulse to check a message notification. It’s the pull to visit YouTube, Facebook, or Twitter for just a few minutes, only to find yourself still tapping and scrolling an hour later. It’s the urge you likely feel throughout your day but hardly notice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>flight safety, lack of bandwidth, and the art of saying no</title>
      <link>https://thearvindas.github.io/blog/the-art-of-saying-no-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 00:19:29 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thearvindas.github.io/blog/the-art-of-saying-no-notes/</guid>
      <description>Here are my notes/highlights/favourite parts from The Art of Saying No by Damon Zahariades:
  Saying no to people is one of the most important skills you can develop. It frees you to pursue your own interests, both personal and professional. To that end, it’ll boost your productivity, improve your relationships, and fill you with a sense of confident calm that may seem alien to you at this moment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5w1h, user stories, and defining KPIs</title>
      <link>https://thearvindas.github.io/blog/5w1h-user-stories-and-defining-kpis/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2021 00:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thearvindas.github.io/blog/5w1h-user-stories-and-defining-kpis/</guid>
      <description>These are my notes from Solving Product Design Exercises by Artiom Dashinsky .
approaching a product design exercise Whenever you encounter a problem, don&amp;rsquo;t immediately dive into it and start thinking of solutions. The single most important thing to remember while solving product design exercises is to follow a process. Here are three tips to help you solve a problem:
  Make sure you understand the task: understand the deliverables, mode of delivery, fidelity level required, and the mode of presentation</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>high agency, the PM craft, and great people</title>
      <link>https://thearvindas.github.io/blog/high-agency-the-pm-craft-and-great-people/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2021 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thearvindas.github.io/blog/high-agency-the-pm-craft-and-great-people/</guid>
      <description>Recently watched this video of Shreyas Doshi talking about his PM learnings over the years, and immediately knew I had to document it right away.
Here are my notes from the video:
Advice for aspiring PMs:
 Do the role before you get the job Your current company/work is the best place to start Build your own side project/product  The Law of PM Suitability: the traits required to break into the PM role are the very same traits that are prerequisites for succeeding as a PM</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
