<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>keeps-updating on Arvin Das</title>
    <link>https://thearvindas.github.io/tags/keeps-updating/</link>
    <description>Recent content in keeps-updating on Arvin Das</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© {year}</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 05:19:29 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://thearvindas.github.io/tags/keeps-updating/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>my favourite reads, tools, and other random things on the internet [keeps updating]</title>
      <link>https://thearvindas.github.io/blog/internet-gratitude-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 05:19:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thearvindas.github.io/blog/internet-gratitude-list/</guid>
      <description>created: dec 17th, 2021
last updated: jan 19th, 2022
The following is a non-exhaustive gratitude list [keeps updating] of all my favourite reads, websites, tools, and any other random thing I&amp;rsquo;ve found on the internet that has helped me make my life better.
reads  The Theory of Cumulative Stress: How to Recover When Stress Builds — James Clear → great read about how stress builds up and how you can fight back Landing at Razorpay — Manan Agarwal → fantastic read about hard work, humility, and trusting the process Rules — Aditya Mohanty → this read is what inspired me to define rules for my own life From Fool To Cool: How To Stay Calm, No Matter What — Bruce Kasanoff → fascinating read about staying calm Lines, not dots — Manas Saloi → a great post (as always from Manas) about building professional relationships Tonkin&amp;rsquo;s Model of Grief — Lois Tonkin → a read about Tonkin&amp;rsquo;s Model of Grief 100 Simple Truths — traf → the cut-throat truth laid down Stonks Simplified → a fascinating newsletter series by my friend Ishaan , fantastic for beginners looking to understand the stock market The Glorious Freedom of Disabling Read Receipts → the article that convinced me to disable my read receipts (was highly reluctant, having kept them on ever since I started using messaging apps) How Slack Became the Fastest Growing B2B SaaS Business Ever → incredible article explaining the brilliance behind Slack How Razorpay is Building Great Products → brilliant insight into how Razorpay&amp;rsquo;s product team works   tools  Markdown New Tab → love using this for my new tabs, easy to jot down to-dos, reminders, etc Visualize Value → when I&amp;rsquo;m not using Markdown New Tab, Visualize Value is my go to extension for new tabs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>small wins, dopamine hits, and documenting 2022 [keeps updating]</title>
      <link>https://thearvindas.github.io/blog/small-wins-dopamine-hits-and-documenting-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 00:19:29 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thearvindas.github.io/blog/small-wins-dopamine-hits-and-documenting-2022/</guid>
      <description>created: jan 2nd, 2022
last updated: jan 13th, 2022
This list is a documentation of all the things that made me happy in 2022 — the small wins that keep me moving. This is not to show off but to bring a sense of gratitude in finding comfort in the smaller things. I have good days and I have bad days and on my bad days, there is comfort in knowing that this is something I can come to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>rules, why I need them, and why I&#39;m writing them down [keeps updating]</title>
      <link>https://thearvindas.github.io/blog/rules/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 05:19:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thearvindas.github.io/blog/rules/</guid>
      <description>created: nov 25th, 2021
last updated: dec 16th, 2022
A while ago, I stumbled across Aditya Mohanty&amp;rsquo;s blog and saw this — a collection of rules that he lives by. Being someone that loves defining every aspect of my life and committing to a certain standard of ethics, I decided to make a list of rules for myself as well.
To save your time, I&amp;rsquo;ve listed my rules first, the chit-chat comes later.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
